allapprovedcars.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy

We take the privacy rights of users of this Website very seriously and this Privacy Policy explains to you how certain information about you may be processed.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated in and subject to the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.carmony.co.uk/en/siteinfo/terms-and-conditions) of Use and Terms of Trade. By using the Website, you expressly consent to the use of your Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Your data

 **"Your Data"** means any information about you which is personally identifiable, including, without limitation, your name, postcode, telephone number, email address, vehicle registration number (if applicable) user name, password and other information from which you can be identified and which you may disclose to us or otherwise via the Website at any time.

###  2\. Collection of your data

We collect your data when:

2.1 

you create an online account; 

2.2 

use the fast search, lifestyle search and/or dealer search functionality on the Website;

2.3 

book a test drive via the Website;

2.4 

use the ‘send to a friend’ functionality on the Website;

2.5 

in respect of trade users of the Website, you provide us with your Listing to enable us to upload your Listing onto the Website; 

2.6 

you make a complaint or enquiry or provide other feedback to us; 

2.7 

you submit an entry to a competition or prize draw; or 

2.8 

you disclose your Data to us or otherwise through the Website at any other point. 

###  3\. Use of your data

3.1 

We use your data to: 

3.1.1 

process the registration of your online account and maintain your online account; 

3.1.2 

in respect of trade users of the Website, process your Listing; 

3.1.3 

process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by you; 

3.1.4 

monitor, develop and improve the Website and your experience; 

3.1.5 

investigate any suspected breach of the Terms and Conditions of Use and Terms of Trade as relevant made by or otherwise relating to you; 

3.1.6 

where (and only where) requested by you, to send you and keep you updated with information by email, telephone and/or sms about existing and new services and special offers from us; 

3.1.7 

where (and only where) requested by you, to send you and keep you updated with information by email, telephone and/or sms about existing and new services and special offers from trusted third parties which we think will be of interest to you; and 

3.1.8 

where you are a prize winner, to publish or otherwise make available a list of prize winners.

3.2 

To opt-out of receiving any information pursuant to paragraph 3.1.6 and 3.1.7, you can: 

i. 

amend your preferences accordingly in your on-line account; 

ii. 

use the facility contained in any such communication; or 

iii. 

email us at unsubscribe@carmony.co.uk stating your user name. 

###  4\. Passing on your data to third parties

4.1 

We may pass on your Data to other parties as follows: 

4.1.1 

to our employees and agents to administer your on-line account and orders; 

4.1.2 

some general statistical information about the Website user base, sales patterns, traffic volumes and related matters may be passed on to reputable third parties but these details will not include information personally identifying you; or 

4.1.3 

we may disclose your Data to the police, regulatory bodies or legal advisers in connection with any alleged criminal offence or suspected breach of the Terms and Conditions of Use and (where appropriate) Terms of Trade by you or where required by law.

4.2 

We do not pass or sell your Data to third persons for any other purpose than those set out in 4.1 above. Any marketing under paragraph 3 is conducted by us on behalf of third parties and they do not have any access to your Data unless you yourself choose to contact them.

###  5\. Data security

We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your Data. All the Data collected by us is stored on a secure server. The secure server software encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. 

###  6\. Cookies

6.1 

**What is a cookie?**  
A cookie is a small text file, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone (referred to here as a "device") browser from a website's computer and is stored on your device's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Many web sites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track online traffic flows. 

The last of these means that certain personalised features cannot then be provided to that user and accordingly they may not be able to take full advantage of all of the website's features. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

During the course of any visit to our website, the pages you see, along with a cookie, are downloaded to your device. Many websites do this, because cookies enable website publishers to do useful things like find out whether the device (and probably its user) has visited the website before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit. 

6.2. 

**How does Carmony.co.uk use cookies?**  
Cookies on Carmony.co.uk are primarily used for analytics purposes only and provides information about your user journey across the site and to enhance your user experience. Users have the opportunity to set their devices to except all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. 

6.3. 

**Third Party Cookies on Carmony.co.uk**  
Please note that during your visits to Carmony.co.uk you may notice some cookies that are not related to Carmony.co.uk contractors. When you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, YouTube or Flickr, you may be presented with cookies from these websites. Carmony.co.uk does not control the dissemination of these cookies. You should check the third party websites for more information about these. 

All third party cookie providers are strictly required not to use any information for their own business or other purposes. 

6.4. 

**Carmony.co.uk cookies and how to reject cookies?**  
Carmony.co.uk cookies and how to reject cookies? A list of the main cookies that the Carmony.co.uk set (and what each is used for) together with ways to minimise the number of cookies you receive can be found within the Carmony.co.uk Cookie List and How To Reject Cookies. 

###  7\. Access to and updating your data

7.1 

Where you are a registered online account holder, you may access and update your Data contained in your online account accessed via the Preferences section of your online profile. You must make sure that you update your Data as soon as possible with any and all relevant changes.

7.2 

If you would like to receive a copy of your Data held by us, please [contact us](mailto:enquiries@carmony.co.uk).

###  8\. Location of your data

We hold your Data in the United Kingdom where the Website servers are located. 

###  9\. Data Protection Statement

Carmony offers registered users access to our update services, car alerts, "My Showroom" and to the "send to a friend" or "email a friend" functionality on the Website. In order to register with us you must supply personal information such as your name, postcode, telephone number, and email address. We (and certain business partners who are engaged to process your information on our behalf) will hold and process your personal information for the purpose of providing you with various services and improving those services to you. 

###  10\. Other links

Please be aware that the Website may link to other web sites that may be accessed by you through our Website. We are not responsible for the data policies, content or security of these linked web sites. We do not have any control over the use to which third parties may put your Data where you choose to purchase products or services or otherwise to contact them via this Website. 

###  11\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or how we use your Data please [contact us](mailto:enquiries@carmony.co.uk) or write to us at ‘Carmony, Manheim Retail Services, Adlington Business Park, Adlington, Cheshire SK10 4NL’. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 30/01/2009.
